Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Go along the top now.
This one will probably
go back on itself.
- Ready?
- You don't need to throw it. I'm here.
- Yeah. I have to swing it.
- Yeah. I know this. but I'm tall.
This is a big day. this.
- How many tractors?
- A hundred tractors.
- A hundred tractors?
- A hundred tractors. all for charity.
Do you go
under the sunroof. or?
No. not through there.
I'd much rather do
this with my friends. not you.
Everyone heard
that. didn't they?
Did everyone hear that Christmas
good cheer from Kaleb Cooper?
I need a cable tie.
I've never known how they
work. I'd be a useless policeman.
- There you go.
- That's it?
That's it.
- I could be a policeman.
- Say it.
- Say the thing.
- I did a thing?
♪ I wish you a
hopeful Christmas ♪
♪ I wish you a brave new year ♪
♪ All anguish.
pain and sadness ♪
♪ Leave your heart And
let your road be clear ♪
♪ They said there'd
be snow at Christmas ♪
♪ They said there'll
be peace on earth ♪
♪ Hallelujah. Noel be
it heaven or hell ♪
♪ The Christmas we
get we deserve ♪
The annual
Christmas tractor run
heralded the start of
the Yuletide festivities.
And as everyone settled down
in front of the Boxing Day telly
in their snazzy new jumpers.
I didn't.
Normally I'd be thinking about:
"Which party shall I go to this evening?"
And: "Where shall I go
tomorrow lunch time?"
All I'm doing now is thinking:
"Have the pigs got water?
"Have the cows got hay?"
Morning pigs.
Ready for some food?
Big dogs.
Come on. Out you go. Out you go.
Feeling peckish?
Ready. steady.
and over she goes.
Oi! Move up.
Come on.
Give you a bit here.
There we go.
And then...
Dog get out!
Sansa. heel. heel.
How have you got in here?
How did they get in?
It's Christmas time.
Come on weaners.
Come on weaners. Come on.
Food time.
Arya. Sansa. heel. heel!
Come out. dogs.
Excellent.
Now then.
Come on.
Well done. Come on.
I want to know how they can both do that.
but they won't jump into the Range Rover.
Come on Sansa. in.
Sansa. get in.
In.
Come on.
Get in.
Sansa. in.
You are such a clown.
However. while
Christmas was busy.
I did manage to get away
for a week in the new year.
Hello. piggies.
And when I returned.
pig-sitter Kaleb had
some surprising news.
- How was holiday?
- Brilliant.
How have the pigs been?
Yeah... It's been an
interesting experience
looking after them
while you've been away.
- What?
- We've got five piglets!
- We've got five little piglets!
- Piglets?
- Yeah. piglets. five.
All doing really well.
- How's that happened?
- I don't know.
They only got mated...
- Did they? Well. you...
- A month ago.
- So she was pregnant when I bought her.
- Yeah.
They were sold as empty.
Well. you've had a
deal and a half then
cos you've got five little piglets
that you didn't know about.
Hello.
Oh. look!
Oh. they're adorable!
They're
cute. aren't they?
Well done. mum!
Oh. look at you!
Look at you!
Oh. look.
Look.
Aw.
- They're better than sheep.
- Yes.
Yes.
Your mother's really
not bothered. is she?
Look at...
Hello you.
As they
had sticky up ears.
it was quickly obvious the father
hadn't been a pedigree Sandy and Black.
But whoever he was.
he'd produced some very
brilliant offspring.
Do you want me
to put him back down?
So they live
in there for how long?
They'll be in
there for another...
We'll move them into the
other place. won't we?
We've got to get them out of
your field. and into the woods.
Yeah.
I do want to get
them out of this field.
because it's bleak
for them up here.
Oh. look at the
really small one.
She is
properly little.
You got him?
Look at the micro pig.
He's nice and warm.
- There's always a runt.
- Oh. but she's just...
Look at the little nose.
It's like the
proud parents. Smiling.
Proud parents!
Sadly. this happy
moment was short-lived.
because the next day. little
runt piggy went missing.
And if you don't want
to know what happened.
put your fingers
in your ears now.
I just find it incredible
that a pig won't eat an onion.
- but it will eat its own child.
- I know. I know.
The only thing they
don't eat is teeth.
- but they won't have had teeth.
- There's no teeth in there.
There's just the bit of an ear.
That's all there was.
That's how I know it was eaten.
My first thought was it's been taken
by a Red Kite. a Buzzard or something.
but there's no way it could
have got into the pigloo.
It was poorly anyway.
That's very sad.
I just hope it was
dead before she ate it.
Stop.
For now. though. we'd have to
put the pig cannibalism to one side.
because if Kaleb was right.
and a piglet tsunami
was on its way.
we'd have to get their new home
built in the woods sharpish.
We're gonna have this
fence here. It's gonna have
a gate there. gate there.
gate there. that's 80 metres.
Yeah.
So. this one gate
accesses that and that.
That one does that and that.
Put a new fence along there and
up. which is easily done. yes?
Yeah. so we'll
measure 80 metres. hang on.
That's
perfect. isn't it?
And Gerald can keep
an eye on them.
- Gerald. your lovely woodland view.
- Nice south-westerly blowing.
Because Gerald's house is not
very far away through there.
He's going to have
some pig honks.
Oh bless him. Hey actually.
talking of Gerald.
- He had his op. didn't he?
- Yeah. he had his op three days ago.
- Yeah. I rang...
- You talked to him?
Yes. I spoke to
him two days ago.
- I'm going to take him some pork.
- Oh good.
He wants some belly pork. so he
must be feeling a little better.
- And apparently...
- He seems happier now actually as well.
Yeah. the word is
he's on the mend.
That's what
we like to hear.
There's a few walls fell down.
so we need him to be back at it.
I know. we do want him back.
With the plans agreed.
we had to start by trimming
the overhead branches
so they wouldn't get in our way.
And because this is a TV show.
that meant plenty of fuss
from Health and Safety.
All right. Jesus. got
him manhandling me.
And then to make
sure you can't escape...
I can't do this. Take it off.
- What?
- I can't have it on.
You can't not have it on
because we're being filmed.
Are we ready? Looking good.
- Can you manage. Lisa?
- Yeah.
I think we're done.
We're done.
There you go. princess.
Hey.
Shit! You all right?
It's okay. I'll get you out.
- You all right?
- No. he forgot he was attached.
- You forgot you were tethered.
- Just come back a little bit. K.
- Did you hit your head?
- Just come back a little bit.
I need you down a
little bit further.
- No. it's alright. I'll do it.
- Just step up a little bit.
So let's
be brutally honest.
The Health and Safety
equipment has injured him.
You've got a
bruise coming up already.
I did exactly the
same thing. remember?
- Yeah. you did it.
- Yeah.
We've got to get rid of all
Health and Safety equipment off the farm.
It's really injuring people.
Luckily. Kaleb's skull was
thicker than the cage it had hit.
so work continued.
Keep going.
keep going. keep going.
Come up to
me a little bit.
However. while
building the new pig houses.
I was reminded that the
woods were in urgent need
of some maintenance.
And the main job. as I'd
discovered back in the autumn.
was repairing a
rapidly collapsing dam.
This is supposed to all
be filled with gravel.
And the gravel has
all been washed away.
There should be five
railway sleepers there.
and then the water goes into
the pipe and comes out there.
If I don't mend this.
when the rains start again.
this will all be washed
away. and the pond will go.
There'll be nowhere for the trout
or the kingfishers that live here.
the ducks that live here.
I've got to mend it.
However. I was
now wise enough to know
that before doing
anything like this
in a wooded environment
full of mice and voles.
I'd need to consult with
mister "No No No" himself.
Morning. Tom.
- Morning. Jeremy.
- How are you?
- I'm all right. Good to see you.
- You as well.
What er... Dogs. come here.
Heel.
I'm training them.
Hang on. sorry.
Well. I understand
that you have some plans
- to do some works around...
- Heel.
...this rather fetching
little pond down here.
Sansa. Arya. heel.
Are you planning
to come down here...
My plan is... Okay.
here's what I want to do.
I just want to be able to get along here
cos I've got to be able to mend that dam.
- Okay. All right.
- Which. as you can see. is broken.
Predictably.
Tom's red flags
were already out in force.
So you've got some
previous kind of evidence here
of having some crayfish.
I think there's loads in here.
- Hmm.
- American ones.
Yeah. yeah. North
American signal. yeah.
And they're
the bad ones.
- They are the bad ones. yeah.
- That have killed all our English ones?
- They're the grey squirrels of crayfish.
- Yeah effectively. Yeah.
- Is that right?
- But they're nastier.
How big are
they? I've never seen one.
16 to 18 centimetres.
like the bigger males.
- What's that in English?
- Er...
- Six inches?
- Basically about this big.
- What. they're like lobsters?
- Yeah. yeah. yeah.
You're going to see the
aggressive males first.
- How aggressive are they?
- They eat their own young.
Yeah. lot of that
going on at the moment...
Because I've been told
there are crayfish in here.
and I was going to catch them
and then sell them in the shop.
Yeah. you can't do that. yeah.
Prison sentences?
Yeah. there's prison
sentences to that. and a fine.
- Yeah.
- I think it's about £2.500.
£2.000? So if I were
to catch one of these crayfish
- then I could be fined £2.500.
- Yeah.
Potentially a
prison term as well.
And possible prison.
- Possible. possible prison. of course.
- Depending on the scale of the situation.
Another problem you have
is I can see some evidence that
some of the banks have eroded.
- That's the biggest kind of issue.
- Ooh...
- Are they eating the banks?
- Yeah.
With these crayfish
burrowing into these banks.
cos they can burrow about 2 metres
at water level back in. right?
And then it can be quite a complex
set of burrows that they've got.
If you're going to
bring machinery down.
you need to be really careful how
close you get to some of these banks.
- because they might just give way.
- In case I squash an invasive crayfish?
No cos you might end up with
your machinery in the lake.
- which we don't want. so...
- Oh.
I'd be highly cautious about
doing anything around these banks.
How would you
recommend I did this work?
My preference would be that a
lot of this would be more manual
than heavy machinery.
- That's the safest way of doing it.
- All right.
With Tom's advice about not
using heavy machinery taken on board.
I set to work.
Ahooya.
Let me talk you through it.
Italian made. low
centre of gravity.
Top speed: 4 km/h.
That's twice as fast as a snail.
Speed. though.
was not its party trick.
No. what Wally the radio-controlled
robo-mulcher does best
is clear away absolutely
everything in its path.
Holy Moly!
What manner of thing is this?
Bloody hellfire!
This is a destroyer of worlds.
They could have had HS2
built in about 20 minutes
if they'd had one of these.
Forward!
I can't even see what
it's doing in there.
It's a whole new game. this is.
When you can't see where it's
gone. you just only use sound
to hear what it's doing.
Oh shitting hell!
Fuck!
So I've broken the one
bit of dam that remained.
Shit!
However.
despite the terrible damage
I've caused over there.
I have... Ow!
Blinded myself.
But apart from the light
blinding and the damaged dam.
I have finally. after
two or three years.
opened up this dam again.
so we can effect a repair.
Kaleb then joined
me to get the ball rolling.
And. to begin with.
everything went swimmingly.
Yes!
We dug
through the subsoil
to get to the farm's seemingly
limitless supply of waterproof clay.
Juicy clay.
Which we'd
use to create the dam.
Go on. keep going.
We then took
the old pipe out.
Stop!
Gravity.
easy transportation.
And manoeuvred
the new pipe into place.
Keep going that way.
- Yeah! Look at that!
- That's bang on.
But from that moment
on. the arguing started.
because when it came
to dam building.
we both knew best.
You see how it's sat in the channel.
We've just got to fill clay in there.
No. you're going to
have to lift this up.
but it isn't just a little bit.
It's a precise measurement.
You've got to lift this up with the
clay. We can do that by hand. though.
- No.
- And then bed it with clay.
Yes. but you say a little bit.
but not like a little bit.
I'm talking about
that much higher.
- I won't be that much.
- It will.
- I reckon that much.
- No. that's wrong.
You're wrong.
When we get the right
height. Kaleb...
- Honestly. take that out.
- Shush. Please. listen. Please.
The bottom of this has to be an inch
below the level of the overflow pipe.
Yes!
I know how to do it. but you
just keep shutting me down.
To settle the dispute.
we installed a laser
measuring device.
And after that.
we started building
a temporary dam
to create a dry working
area for the proper dam.
which is when the
squabbling got worse.
Leave those. We're going
to need them to build on top of.
Yeah. but we're
going to do it there. look.
No. Please.
stop interfering.
So sensitive
all the time.
Thank you.
How many
more do you need?
Don't touch the laser...
Don't touch the laser thing!
God strewth.
Oh no! He's done it.
Don't hit the laser!
Oh for fuck's sake!
I've never seen
incompetence like it.
Why didn't I do... Oh!
Oh. God.
Right. Can you
put it on crab steer?
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
At the minute. you've got
the wheels doing that.
You want to get them all
turning the same way.
Yeah.
That's not crab steer.
You're not in crab steer.
No. Kaleb. stop it! You've
got to get it in crab steer.
Don't move
it until you get it in crab steer.
It's in crab steer.
but I cannot turn
the steering wheel.
Watch.
Please put it in crab steer.
It's in crab steer!
I just cannot move!
No. you have to turn the steering
wheel to lock it into crab steer!
Jesus Christ!
You're going to have to get
a chainsaw and lop that branch off.
Don't worry. Kaleb. I'm
on my way to rescue you
from your own incompetence.
Where would you go? Here?
The knuckle.
- No.
- At the knuckle.
Here?
- You idiot!
- What?
You're meant to cut
from the bottom.
Oh! Fuck you!
You knew that was
going to happen!
- That wasn't funny.
- I told you...
I told you to go around
that side and cut.
I didn't do fuck all!
You spent all morning
throwing fucking rocks at me.
And now...
Hello?
The tree landed
on my bloody head.
Hi. what's going on?
Oh. he's being a fucking
foetus is what's going on.
You're just incompetent
with a chainsaw.
You cut from the bottom
cos it was pinching.
It pinched
onto my head.
No. it pinched the chainsaw
blade. It's fucking bullshit!
What are
we doing anyway?
Ah well. now I can explain
that. and you'll be pleased.
Behold!
You're repairing the dam?
Yes!
The pipe that was in
there was all broken.
So we've got that out.
we've got some clay
to create a temporary dam
while we build the proper dam.
- Okay.
- But then the foetus.
whose only been driving
for a few minutes.
has managed to drop the
telehandler off the track.
Yeah.
that's what happened.
And then he went against a
tree branch. which I had to cut off.
and he thought it would be humorous
if I was cutting near the knuckle.
'cause he could see from the cab
that it would push it
round and knock me over
with a running chainsaw...
- That's untrue.
- Yes. it's true.
- No. it's not.
- It is.
- You were using a chainsaw?
- Yes.
- Like that?
- Well. I had a hat on.
Fucking bullshit!
Safety trousers?
My jeans.
You could have cut your leg off.
Exactly. but I wouldn't have
done if it weren't for Kaleb.
You're gonna have to
seriously reprimand him.
Well. no. I'm reprimanding
you for not wearing any...
I was wearing. I had a visor.
Yeah. and then you slip.
- I didn't slip.
- What's the weather?
All right. but anyway.
luckily. that didn't happen.
And why
we do it. I mean.
I am
flabbergasted at this.
How long has this taken to
create this mess?
- You are mending. fixing. repairing...
- Yes.
- A dam...
That is protecting.
holding back water.
and if this goes wrong.
which there is a
likelihood that it will...
- It didn't.
- No offence.
Straight down there.
down at Eastend. the
only part of Chadlington
- that actually quite likes you...
- Brookend. Yeah.
You're gonna flood.
And you haven't
notified anybody.
It's a statutory requirement
to notify the local authority.
You've got to notify the West
Oxfordshire District Council.
- How do you get on with them?
- They're gonna say no.
Well. they are gonna say no.
because they're gonna say:
"What precautions have you
taken to stop a flood risk?"
None!
Whatsoever!
I've still
got a chainsaw.
If you knew how to use
it right. you'd be fine.
It's a
good job I've come.
- I'm not speaking to him again.
- Stupid man!
- Oh. and the other thing.
- Go on. then.
No. no. no. no. How are we
going to rectify this mess?
- What mess?
- This!
Look. you've chucked all the... I mean
how are you going to get that out?
You've just dumped
rubbish in a water course.
- What is that? Any asbestos in there?
- No.
- Well. that's brick rubble.
- That was already in there.
You're
blocking the...
- Don't shout at me.
- No. it's both of you.
- No. it's not me!
- Well. you're here.
- You got the digger in.
- I get employed by him to do it.
You're aiding
and abetting him.
- I didn't do anything.
- He's farm manager.
Here it goes.
the blame goes to me.
Hold on. who
was driving it? You were.
But Charlie. I said: "I
don't think this is a good idea
- to bring this down here."
- It wasn't a good idea.
We decided.
after all this.
to stop dam work until
the ground was less muddy.
and went back to installing the
new fully insulated pigloos.
And when that was done.
it was time to move
in the new residents.
Right. let's get them back.
Is that...?
That's quite loud!
Come on pigs.
Come on piggies.
Yeah.
- Go. go. go.
- Come on!
There you go.
Piggies!
Look at this. a whole pig city.
Woodland pigs.
Hey boys. look they're
snuffling around.
- Have they started truffling?
- Yes. look. Look.
Oh. look at
their little faces!
They look happier here
than they did in their...
- I feel here happier looking at them.
- I do.
With the pigs settling
into their new woodland home.
Kaleb could have
their old field back.
so he could use it to make money
for his side of the operation.
I'm gonna clear this up. and
then. I'm gonna plant grass.
- What?
- I'm gonna plant grass. make hay.
- Oh. hay.
- Sell the hay. Yeah.
Is hay
really a good idea?
I think so.
Three cuts. get £200 a ton.
So I'm going to small bale it. then
I'm gonna sell them for £7 a bale.
To all the people
moving out of London
- who then get horses.
- Exactly.
So who's moved up? Joe Wicks
has moved up here apparently.
I don't know who that is.
You could introduce
me to them all.
Look at that for a business
plan. Made me happier already.
Yeah. but what the ladies
and gentlemen are doing now
is shitting themselves laughing
- at the notion that I know Joe Wicks.
- I don't know who that is.
He's that fitness man in Covid.
and he did those exercises online.
and everybody
started watching him.
Anyway. he's moved up here.
We've got Cowell.
we've got Beckham.
Natalie Imbruglia...
We've got Amanda Holden.
- We can sell hay to their horses.
- Yeah.
Leaving Kaleb
to prep his field.
I turned my attention back
to the enforcement notice.
Charlie had now
submitted our appeal.
and I had my fingers crossed
that the farm shop at
least could stay open.
as it was the only way that my
"farming the unfarmed" projects
could ever make money.
So I'm
actually £8.230 up.
To make
sure we had a case.
the shop had to
be squeaky clean.
Which meant everything
for sale in there
had to have come from inside a
council-imposed 16-mile radius.
We all understood that.
Except Lisa.
Lisa has a rather Irish attitude
- to rules and regulations.
- Yeah.
I went in there the other
day whilst it was closed. after hours.
Under the counter
everything.
red-handed.
If you want any of the products you and
I have put a moratorium on selling...
No because we keep saying to
her: "You can't sell this."
And she literally can't see why.
So here is a planning
enforcement notice.
"If you don't comply.
you get prosecuted."
It's not like a civil thing.
And I keep saying to Lisa:
"If you carry on selling stuff that is
in breach of this enforcement notice.
"we..." Well. it'll be
me in The Daily Mail.
But "we will be fined."
And I... So. if you could have
a st... I mean. I talked to her.
"Oh.
it'll be all right."
Which is lovely. I mean
I'd love to live in Ireland
'cause I think a
country functions better
- if you have that attitude.
- So. you'd like me to say...
You know sometimes you're
quite firm with me.
Could you be that firm
with Lisa and say:
"Lisa. you have got to take
out all this illegal stuff"?
Hmm.
Hi. Charlie.
We're under the
spotlight. Properly.
Yeah.
Quite a lot of it is directed
at the farm shop as well.
And I know we've had discussions
over the past few months
about what you can
and can't sell.
and we've done the potato thing.
which has gone brilliantly.
Yes. it has. Everyone loves it.
So. but you've got
prices now on the...
I have. yeah.
You can't do that.
Really you can't sell them.
Yes.
- You cannot sell them.
- Yeah.
We can't give
them any more ammunition.
So anything.
- anything that is 16 miles away must go.
- Yeah.
I mean as much
as I want to respect
government. councils
and everything else.
at what stage
do you just really struggle
with trying to respect
what they're doing?
Because there could be...
I'm not trading arms here.
It's just a farm shop.
I'll come back to that.
Where's the Monopoly from?
Cotswolds Monopoly.
Look. Diddly Squat.
Yeah I know.
but it's made in...
- China...
- It's like the book Jeremy wrote.
We can't sell the book.
We can't sell the book here. I
mean. we have to follow the rules.
If we don't follow the rules.
you could actually end up
with a criminal conviction.
which is ridiculous.
I understand that.
Because all we're doing is
selling some amazing farm produce.
you know. oils. chutneys.
marm... marmala...
We don't even grow oranges.
That's old stock from last year.
Yeah. but it doesn't
matter whether it's old stock.
- They would prefer that I waste it.
- Where is it made?
South Somerset.
- It's not within our 16 miles.
- No.
The longer I look. the worse
it becomes. doesn't it?
Handkerchiefs.
They look quite Italian to me.
Were they embroidered locally?
No...
- Lisa. we've really...
- Charlie. I understand. I understand.
It's just I find it really
difficult that everything we do.
it doesn't make any
difference. It's still no.
But we are fighting. you know.
people who are not being rational
about the objective. you know.
position of this farm.
All we're wanting to do is
sell some local produce.
which is what we're
allowed to do.
from a shop that we
have permission in.
When we challenge them. which
we are doing on the planning.
we can then say: "This is
ridiculous. Let's get a car park in."
I know it's frustrating.
Lots of rules in
life are frustrating.
but these we must
follow just for now.
So. in no particular order:
Marmalade. book.
presumably socks...
No. yes...
Monopoly.
handkerchiefs.
Did you manage
to get across to her
- the importance of not selling...
- I did see produce
coming out of the
shop before I left.
Books particularly. Monopoly.
So there's the. I. ye...
Yes. I think actually she...
I think we've got
the message through.
Right. she's not here.
I'll bet you any money
she's loading her car up with all
the stuff she took out this morning
and is putting it back.
Hmm.
Praying that Charlie
had got through to Lisa.
I got back to my winter jobs.
which alternated
between tedious...
Oh Christ!
Delicious snack
for you "sheeps".
Oh for fuck sake!
And
unbelievably rewarding.
Oh yes!
Mincing.
Minced.
In addition.
there was another winter task
that I'd decided was worth doing.
My job today is to try and save
the life of this willow tree.
which amazingly.
even though it's fallen over.
isn't dead.
Obviously. to do
this. I needed some help.
So I called Rupert.
the local tree expert.
What's the plan then.
to make it come back up again?
We're going to
pollard it right low.
We're going to take off all the
weight at the top of the willow.
And that's pollarding.
It's pollarding. It's going to
maintain the tree. make it last longer.
- 18 years or so.
- But there's no roots.
How's it going to
put roots down?
They'll come back.
- Will they?
- Yeah. yeah.
After Rupert had
used his hydraulic secateurs
to prune the tree
of excess weight...
Bloody glad I'm not in there!
We joined forces.
like the Cotswold Thunderbirds.
with me in a rented Bobcat
pulling a cable
attached to the tree.
and Rupert using his JCB
to provide extra leverage.
If we can get this tree
upright. it'll be a miracle.
If we get it upright.
and it survives...
I was gonna say
I'll go to church.
I won't do that.
Okay
Jeremy. if you can drive forward.
Full power.
I'm guessing
from the wheels pin
we're not making the
tree become vertical.
Just waiting for the cable to
snap and scythe through the cab.
severing my abdomen.
With the willow
still stubbornly horizontal.
I decided to deploy
my chainsaw skills
on its remaining branches.
Then Rupert tried to pull
the tree up on his lonesome.
Here he comes! Here he comes!
Here he is!
Is it going to fall straight over
again? Is it going to go upright. or?
Tree is up!
That's just brilliant.
- Really well thanks for that.
- It's good.
And honestly you'd never know
we'd had a digger in here.
or any machinery at all.
Please. God. don't let
Charlie Ireland down here
for at least 6 months.
February
was now upon us.
And with the pigs enjoying
their new woodland home.
and my winter jobs mainly done.
I went off to do some
filming for The Grand Tour.
And while I was gone.
one of the pointy-eared
mongrel piglets fell ill.
So Lisa called in
Dilwyn the vet.
So. he's got blue ears.
- He's been shivering a bit.
- Oh...
He's a bit unsteady on his legs.
- You can see his belly's quite empty.
- Why...
I don't think he's been
suckling his mother.
What's the blue ears?
The blue ears is he's probably
got a bit of septicaemia.
which is basically. he's
in shock a little bit.
because he's probably
got a bug floating
around in his blood.
I'll take him back. I'll put
the heater on in the car.
- Yeah.
- And I'll take him back.
and I'll keep you posted.
Poor little one.
Lisa then insisted
that Dilwyn give the piglet
the full 5-star
platinum plus treatment.
So that's the pump. and that warms
up the fluids going into him.
So basically. we're trying
to warm up his blood.
We're warming up his body
and this is trying to correct
his dehydration really.
Yeah. we'll see how we get on.
I returned a week later
and got straight back
into more pig jobs.
Right.
Home time.
The first of
which was to return Ajax.
the boar I'd rented to
impregnate the lady pigs.
Aw. he must be so looking
forward to going back to some friends.
Do you know how much it
cost. how much we had to pay?
For each successful
shag he had is 50 quid.
We have to pay his pimp at Avis.
- from whom we rented him. 50 quid.
- Yeah.
And so he's done... five?
- Four.
That's 80 quid.
No. it's 200.
While we're on the
subject of money. Lisa.
- you know when I was away...
- Hmm-hmm.
- And that piglet was ill.
- Yes.
- And you sent it to the vet.
- I did.
That's the vet bill.
God almighty! And it died.
Feeder tube. Aw colostomy! They
put a feeding tube down his...
No. no. no. Never
mind what they did.
What's that say? £673.
- I just let them die?
- Gone.
I don't know what
you do actually.
Put that one down
when it was like that.
- Say goodbye.
- I didn't know. everyone was away.
- £673.40.
- They tried to keep it alive.
Yes. they did!
- A post-mortem? That's a bit flash.
- Yes!
- Who asked for a post-mortem?
- Have you got that picture of it?
So here's one picture look.
That's at the vet nurse's house.
'cause they had to take
it home for the night.
Oh!
But she was getting paid all
night to look after that pig.
Look at the little
thing on his ear like a...
- We're farmers!
- I know.
- I mean I like the piglets. but £673!
- I'll eat it myself in future.
That's bad. That's a lot.
Well. now they've done a
post-mortem. why did it die?
Gonna bring
that gate around.
It had a heart defect.
Well. who was to know?
Well. we do now.
- because we've spent £673.
- Go on then.
Cock!
You go that side.
The extravagance
was all the more annoying.
because it was now time to
see how Kaleb and I were doing
in our competition.
So we've got to add
another 1.800 quid to that.
Kaleb was still
massively in the red.
but now the pigs were here.
my outgoings were
also on the rise.
So you're at £98.500
you've spent so far
and made nothing.
Don't you worry about me.
Let's worry about you.
- That pig.
- Oh. we've got the pig bill.
- £673.40.
- Yeah.
Lisa has screwed me on
this one. I'll grant you.
- Another one coming.
- Another one what?
I've got loads more. I've got
loads of bills here for you.
- What?
- That machine that you're obsessed with.
It is my emotional
support machine.
like an emotional support dog.
I'm going to take it on
planes with me on holiday.
It can have its own seat.
Well. how much was it?
£1.050.
But I think that can be cancelled
out by how happy it makes me.
No. it definitely cannot.
Well. does it... Does it
keep me out of your hair?
Yeah. it did. I like the
machine. don't get me wrong.
- 'Cause you're nowhere near me.
- Yeah.
Did you have someone
come down with a digger.
and remove a tree?
No. no. no. we put
a tree back up.
Okey do key. Well.
that is a total of £3.090.
Just there if I was you.
- Put it there.
- £3.090?
- What else have you got?
- There's the pig food.
£2.952.
Have they been
going to the Savoy?
- And then you had the hire of the boar.
- Oh. stop saying things. What?
- The hire of the boar. £200.
- Boar hire.
This mountain of bills
meant that my profits of £413
had been turned into a
loss of nearly £8.000.
Shit!
Go on. pigs.
However. in
a bittersweet way.
I was about to start seeing
a return on my investment.
Come on.
As it was time to
take the first batch of pigs
to the slaughterhouse.
You're in for an
exciting car ride. Come on.
However. since the
abattoir was more than 40 miles away
and I didn't have a licence
to transport them that far.
the government's pig police said
I must be accompanied by Michaela.
a local breeder.
Oh no. I've got guilt.
You should feel sad
when they go to the abattoir.
It means you've cared
about your animals.
I do care about them.
You've got to
eat them to save them.
That enables the
survival of the breed.
You can't keep them all alive.
Well. that's what
I've always said about pandas.
If you want to save the
giant panda. start eating it.
Do you know for every
middle white pig in the world.
there are 3 giant pandas.
Middle white pork.
you can't beat it.
It's better than sex.
Right.
With anyone. even
Ewan McGregor. yeah.
I'm not sure Ewan's going to
be very pleased to hear that.
Right. okey do key.
Seven. all seven there?
- Yeah.
- Righty-oh.
Come on. out you go.
I've really enjoyed keeping
pigs. They've not escaped once.
- Do you like pigs?
- I love them.
Come on
then. pigs. There we go.
They're
nice pigs actually.
These stronger ones you'll be having
for bacon and sausages I'd have thought.
I'm assuming you
want everything...
The butcher will
want everything back.
bar the squeal.
- Oh. don't.
- Sorry.
Every time
I go to an abattoir
your cruel abattoir humour.
Bye. pigs.
Right.
thank you very much.
As usual. I
was sad as I drove away.
But this time. at least. I'd
behaved more like a farmer
and not had any unmanly moments.
However. that was
all about to change.
because an avalanche
of heartache
was heading my way.
Oh my God. they're so far up.
One of them is as weak as hell.
This is why you're
losing so many piglets.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm